General Reference; Collection ua950.002
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- T, 1950-1998; 20
  - Tower Tribune, 1971-1977; Undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - A Tradition of Excellence, Undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Training Resource and Counselling Network, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Transfer Student Program - summer planning conference, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Tri - Beta, 1980 September 4 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Truth Cluster(Freedom Quad), 1988 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Tumbleweeds from Construction, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Tuition, 1962-1969 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Tuition Protests, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - University at Albany - Two Year College Dev. Center, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Two Year College Development Center, 1989 September (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Two Year College Development Center, 1989 September (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Two - Year College Development Center (Conference), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- U, 1893-2001; 21
  - U2 concert, 1983 May 7
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Materials from May 6th, 1983 issue of the ASP and the 1983 yearbook. Color photos donated by a student.
  - Undergraduate Academic Policy Manual, 1990 August 30-1992 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Undergraduate Academic Regulations, 1972-1979 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Undergraduate Academic Regulations and Requirement, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, Office of University of Albany, SUNY Application Form, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, Office of "What are you looking for ? University at Albany Students have it all!", Undated (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, Office of, ca. 1975 June-1988 March 24 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Office of Undergraduate Admissions, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Undergraduate Courses + Programs - Rules + Regulations, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Undergraduate Viewbooks + Application, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Center for Undergraduate Education(CUE), ca. 1987 September (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Undergraduate Policy, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate Program, Undated (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - UNI - 180 Undergraduate Supervised Search, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Unidentified Flying Object Investigation Team, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Unification Church, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Union For Radical Political Economics, 1972-1979 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - United States - China Peoples Friendship Association, 1971-1977 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - United States Labor Party Forum, 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - United University Professionals, ca. 1996 September 16 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - United University Professions, Undated (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - United Way, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - University Action for the Disabled, 1994 February (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - University Advancement, Division of Operations Plan, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - University Archives Exhibit Announcement "Opportunity Diversity and Service: History of the University at Albany, 1844 - 1994" (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - University Art Gallery: Noontime Brown Bag Lunch Series, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - University Art Museum, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - The University at Albany, Undated (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - University at Albany: A $4 Billion Engine For Economic Growth, 1990 - 1999, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - University at Albany: A $4 Billion Engine For Economic Growth, 1990 - 1999 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - University at Albany Alumni Artists, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - University at Albany: Bibliography, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - University at Albany Calendar, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - University Event Calendar (See University at Albany Calendar), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - University at Albany Calendar (See also University Events Calendar,1988 - 1989), 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - University at Albany Colloquium, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - University At Albany FACTS, 1993-1999 (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - University at Albany Fund Inc., 1988 (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - The University at Albany Fund, INC., 1984 (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - University Auxiliary Services, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - University - Campaign for the Libraries, 2000 May 3 (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - University Celebrity Series, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - University Chorale, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - University Cinemas, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - University Colloquium, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - University Community Council, 1972-1991 May 17 (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - University Community Orchestra, Undated (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - University Community Orchestra, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - University Community Picnic, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - University Concert Board, 1972-1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - University Council, 1977-1996 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - University Counseling Center, 1972-1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Office of University Development, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - University: Economic Impact Study, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - University Event Calendar (See University at Albany Calendar,1989 - ), 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - University Faculty Meeting, 1997 May 7 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - University Faculty Meeting, 1998 October 13 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - University Faculty Meeting, 1992 September 9 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - University Faculty Senate Handbook, Bylaws, Procedures, and History, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - University Family College, ca. 1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - University Food Service, 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - University Forum, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - University Foundation At Albany, 1975; 1985 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - University Health Center, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - University Health Center (Triple H Plan), 1990 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - University in High School, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - University in High School, The, ca. 1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - University Legislative Priorities, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - University Libraries, Undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - University Libraries - Progress Report (see also UL - Annual Report), 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - University Libraries - Progress, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - University Libraries: Progress Report, 1988-1993 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - University Libraries - Progress Report, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - University Libraries - Progress Report, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - University Libraries - Progress Toward Strategic Goals, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - University Libraries - Strategic Plan, 1990-1995 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - University Libraries - Strategic Plan, 1999-2004 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - University Lib. - Two Millionth Volume Celebration, 2001 April 5 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - University Logo, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - University Mace, 1982 May (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - University Micros, 1985 February-1986 November (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - University Motto, 1991 January 15 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - University News, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - University of the Air, 1967 November 28-1968 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - University Parents Association, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - University Placement Service, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - University Regulations, 1981-1985 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - University Relations & Academic Affairs "Be Our Guest: University At Albany", 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - University Seal, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - "Foundation to Buy Sterling - Withrop Buildings for University Research Center"- Mary Fiess, Undated (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - University Seminars, Undated (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - University Senate, 1988-1998 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - University Senate - Annual Reports, 1989 November 17 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - University Senate, Council + Standing Committees List, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Univ. Senate: Educational Policies Council "4x4"Task Force report, 1989 January 5 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - University Senate - Libraries, Computing + Information Systems Coucil, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - University Series, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - University System Analysis (David Fotheringham), Undated (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - University - Wide Committee On the Arts, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Upstate New York Junior Science + Humanities Symposium, 1987 April 2-1987 April 3 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Uptown Campus and History - Albany Country Club; Hunt Club; Knowles Estate, Undated (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Uptown Campus Mans from Albany Hall of Research, 1893-1930 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Uptown Campus: Dedication, 1968 May 15-1968 May 17 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Urban Affairs Committee, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Urban and Regional Planning Committee, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - UUP: SUNY's Future: Expanding the Mission Fulfilling the Promise, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 58)
- V, 1957-2001; 22
  - Judge Newton B. Van Derzee Scholarship Fund, 1957 April (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Veterans Administration Counseling Center, 1963-1972 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Veteran's Club, 1976 January 21 (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Veterans Information Center, Undated (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Veterans Project, 2001 June 9 (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - Office of Vice President, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - Office of the Vice President for student Affairs, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - Vietnam War Service, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - View for the Prospective Staff Member, A, ca. 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - The Voice, Albany Newspaper, 1969 December 10-1969 December 16 (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - Vote Young Socialist Alliance Fight the Cuts: Vote Young Socialist, Undated (Box 33, Folder 69)
  - Voter Registration, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 70)
- W, 1848-1996; 23
  - Ada Craig Walker Award 1st Awarded, 1953-1969 (Box 33, Folder 71)
  - WWII, 1943-1945 (Box 33, Folder 72)
  - Waldron, Julia R., Undated (Box 33, Folder 73)
  - Dr. Edith O Wallace Humanities Building (see also Wallace, Edith O, Faculty File) Edith O. Wallace Papers, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 74)
  - Wankmuller, Steven (student), 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 75)
  - James A. Warden Scholarship Warden'51 (see also Alumni Association - Deceased Alumni file on Warden, 1961 July-1966 (Box 33, Folder 76)
  - George Warnock Incident (Young Republicans), ca. 1951 (Box 33, Folder 77)
  - Water Polo Club, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 78)
  - WCDB, Capital District Board Casting, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 79)
  - Webster, Fanny C., 1848 January (Box 33, Folder 80)
  - Wednesday Wanderings, 1984-1989 (Box 33, Folder 81)
  - Wellness Programming, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 82)
  - Whistle Watch "President's Task Force on Women's Safety Program, ca. 1993 (Box 33, Folder 83)
  - Whistle Watch Program, ca. 1996 (Box 33, Folder 84)
  - Whiteface Mountain Field Station and Summit Observatory, The ASRC, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 85)
  - Whiteface Mountain Observatory - Vincent Schaefer and Ray Falconer, Undated (Box 33, Folder 86)
  - Whitman Hall, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 87)
  - Wild Wild Weekend, 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 88)
  - Wilson, Karen, ca. 1985 April 10-1995 May 18 (Box 33, Folder 89)
  - Winterlude, 1962 December 15 (Box 33, Folder 90)
  - Women Graduates - Prominent, Undated (Box 33, Folder 91)
  - Women's Athletic Association, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 92)
  - Women's Career Enhancement Committee of Women's Concerns Committee, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 93)
  - Women's Caucus, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 94)
  - Women's Concerns Committee, 1985; 1988 (Box 33, Folder 95)
  - Women's Concerns Committee, The, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 96)
  - Women's Concerns Resource Center, ca. 1975 November 15 (Box 33, Folder 97)
  - Women's Concerns Resource Center State University of New York at Albany, 1976 October 27 (Box 33, Folder 98)
  - Women's Connection, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 99)
  - Women's Intramural Recreation Assoc., 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 100)
  - Women's Recreation Association, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 101)
  - Women's Rugby Club, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 102)
  - Workshop Guide, the Albany Challenging Behavior Project, Undated (Box 33, Folder 103)
  - World Food Day, 1984 October 16 (Box 33, Folder 104)
  - World War I, 1916 June-1921 November (Box 33, Folder 105)
  - World Week, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 106)
  - World Week, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 107)
  - World Week, 1990 March (Box 33, Folder 108)
  - World Week IX Cookbook, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 109)
  - Writing and the Holocaust Conference on, 1987 April 5-1987 April 7 (Box 33, Folder 110)
  - Writing Center, 1983-1986 (Box 33, Folder 111)
  - Writing Intensive Program, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 112)
  - WRIT - Writing Research & Interest Table, Undated (Box 33, Folder 113)
  - WSUA, 1970-1975 (Box 33, Folder 114)
- X, 1988; 24
  - X - Ray Clinic, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 115)
- Y, 1927-1999; 25
  - Young Americans For Freedom, 1971-1975 (Box 33, Folder 116)
  - Young Peoples Socialist League, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 117)
  - Young Republicans, 1971-1974 September 4 (Box 33, Folder 118)
  - Young Socialist Alliance, 1969-1987 (Box 33, Folder 119)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, ca. 1927 (Box 33, Folder 120)
  - Youth Construction Initiative Program, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 121)
  - Youth Construction Initiative Program Yearbook (NYS Dept. of Transportation + U at A School of Education), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 122)
- Z, 1971-1991; 26
  - Zenger Hall, 1973-1976 (Box 33, Folder 123)
  - Zero Population Growth, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 124)
  - Zeta Beta Tau Fraternity Epsilon Gamma Chapter recog. By Nat'l 1986 Interfraternity Council, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 125)
  - Zeta Phi Beta Fraternity Phi Beta Chapter Pan Hellenic Council, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 126)
  - Zetetics, Undated (Box 33, Folder 127)
  - Zionism, 1972-1976 April 27 (Box 33, Folder 128)